<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>career on Lindsay T Shelton</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/tags/career/</link><description>Recent content in career on Lindsay T Shelton</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 11:29:05 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blist.vercel.app/tags/career/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How'd I Get Here: From Stage to Stage</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202403from_stage_to_stage/</link><pubDate>Sat, 30 Mar 2024 11:29:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202403from_stage_to_stage/</guid><description>Why Am I Talking About High School? Recently, I was having a great conversation with my new friend Reid, and he asked me a question that really got me thinking: &amp;ldquo;What did you do in your past that prepared you for becoming an MVP?&amp;rdquo;.
I was a theater junkie: such a fan that I sometimes spelt it &amp;ldquo;theatre&amp;rdquo;. It started with a traveling community theater group that would put on a show in a week, and I auditioned every summer - it was the highlight of my year.</description></item><item><title>Vacation, All I Ever Wanted</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202009vacation-all-i-ever-wanted/</link><pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202009vacation-all-i-ever-wanted/</guid><description>Actual photo of me contemplating how cool waves are.
Burnout is a disease we are all capable of catching. It’s one I battled for years as a teacher, and while I hadn’t yet caught it in my new career, I could feel it lurking much sooner than anticipated. It isn’t that I’m unhappy or unfulfilled because I’m neither of those things – I have new challenges (that I’m capable of meeting) every day and I learn new things constantly.</description></item><item><title>A Free Way to Improve Employee Productivity</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202008a-free-way-to-improve-employee-productivity/</link><pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202008a-free-way-to-improve-employee-productivity/</guid><description>Businesses (and people in general) love getting things for free. Cut costs? Awesome. Save money? Super. So what if I were to tell you that there is a FREE way to make employees happier, more productive, and more likely to stay at your company?
Spoiler alert – it’s really not rocket science. Also, as a disclaimer, it may not work for everyone.
However, I discovered recently that there is something essential for my workplace happiness.</description></item><item><title>On Being a Woman in Tech</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202007on-being-a-woman-in-tech/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202007on-being-a-woman-in-tech/</guid><description>I am in a special, rare butterfly situation. At this moment, I only work with other women at Smarter Consulting. It’s me and four other smart, talented women who came from a variety of backgrounds, both in terms of our education and our careers. Some of us didn’t graduate college and some of us hold master’s degrees. Some of us have never worked in a strictly tech field (me).</description></item><item><title>Changing Careers During a Pandemic</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202006changing-careers-during-a-pandemic/</link><pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202006changing-careers-during-a-pandemic/</guid><description>Growing up, I always knew I was going to become a teacher. Sure, my first choice was famous actress, but my solid backup plan was always elementary education. The only time I questioned my plan was when I entered freshman year of college and realized — not only did I not want to teach math and science, but that small children were kind of scary to me. So, after one semester, I changed my major to Secondary English Education and I was back on track for my life plan.</description></item></channel></rss>