<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>microsoft teams on Lindsay T Shelton</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/tags/microsoft-teams/</link><description>Recent content in microsoft teams on Lindsay T Shelton</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 12:49:05 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blist.vercel.app/tags/microsoft-teams/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Cleaning Up Teams Files with Power Automate</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202310cleaning-up-teams-files-with-power-automate/</link><pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 12:49:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202310cleaning-up-teams-files-with-power-automate/</guid><description>One of my power users, Lisa, reached out to me with an interesting use case this week. She&amp;rsquo;s very self-reliant and had done her due dilligence at searching for an answer to her problem before admitting defeat and coming to me (and thus to Power Automate). When she said no one had a good answer for this in her searches, I knew that not only did I have to help her, but that I&amp;rsquo;d finally have a good blog post idea if I found the solution!</description></item><item><title>New Blog Post on Tekki Gurus</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202307new-blog-post-on-tekki-gurus-copy/</link><pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202307new-blog-post-on-tekki-gurus-copy/</guid><description>I&amp;rsquo;m putting out a few blogs on a site called Tekki Gurus! It&amp;rsquo;s got lots of great stuff, my new blog post included. So if you want to know how to build your very first Power Automate flow, or you want to know how to get notifications from a Microsoft Form submission, then check it out! How to Create Microsoft Forms Notifications in Under 15 Minutes Using Power Automate</description></item><item><title>How To: Display Your M365 Group in Outlook (If You Can't Find It)</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202102how-to-display-your-m365-group-in-outlook/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 Feb 2021 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202102how-to-display-your-m365-group-in-outlook/</guid><description>If you’ve spent much time with the Microsoft 365 eco-system, then you know as well as I do that there are countless ways to create new M365 groups. Everyone has their own preferences, certainly, and there isn’t really a need to pick only one method. What gets created and set-up as a result of creating a group, however, DOES change depending on which method you pick, which leads me to the use case that prompted this blog.</description></item><item><title>How To: Share Your Screen AND See Your Audience in Microsoft Teams</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202009how-to-share-your-screen-and-see-your-audience-in-microsoft-teams/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202009how-to-share-your-screen-and-see-your-audience-in-microsoft-teams/</guid><description>If you are able to have more than one monitor, your life as virtual educator or work from home employee is a lot easier. One of those ways that life is easier is that you can both share your screen to present whatever information is relevant while also seeing your audience. It isn’t immediately clear, however, exactly how to see your audience at the same time, which is what this post will clear up for you.</description></item><item><title>How To: Change Team Names in Teams for Education</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202008how-to-change-team-names-in-teams-for-education/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202008how-to-change-team-names-in-teams-for-education/</guid><description>It’s almost fall and your IT department is swamped making hundreds if not thousands of Teams for teachers and their classes. However, sometimes their naming conventions they’ve utilized might not work best for teachers. We all know that IT doesn’t have the time to go in and fix the name of your Team to suit you best, so I’ve put together a tutorial for how you can make those changes yourself.</description></item></channel></rss>