<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>personal on Lindsay T. Shelton</title>
    <link>https:/tags/personal/</link>
    <description>Recent content in personal on Lindsay T. Shelton</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 14:49:05 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https:/tags/personal/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Microsoft Power Platform Conference – Trip of a Lifetime</title>
      <link>https:/blog/202306microsoft-power-platform-conference-trip-of-a-lifetime/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jun 2023 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https:/blog/202306microsoft-power-platform-conference-trip-of-a-lifetime/</guid>
      <description>I was going through a really rough time. I had experienced a loss that so many do experience – one of my 14 year old littermate kitties, Archie, had taken a sudden turn and had to be put to sleep. It was almost my birthday and I had lost one of my beloved cats and I was feeling very sorry for myself.
However, it was time to pull myself together and pack my bags, because I was headed to the inaugural Power Platform Conference in Orlando, FL all my myself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vacation, All I Ever Wanted</title>
      <link>https:/blog/202009vacation-all-i-ever-wanted/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https:/blog/202009vacation-all-i-ever-wanted/</guid>
      <description>Actual photo of me contemplating how cool waves are.
Burnout is a disease we are all capable of catching. It’s one I battled for years as a teacher, and while I hadn’t yet caught it in my new career, I could feel it lurking much sooner than anticipated. It isn’t that I’m unhappy or unfulfilled because I’m neither of those things – I have new challenges (that I’m capable of meeting) every day and I learn new things constantly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A Free Way to Improve Employee Productivity</title>
      <link>https:/blog/202008a-free-way-to-improve-employee-productivity/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Aug 2020 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https:/blog/202008a-free-way-to-improve-employee-productivity/</guid>
      <description>Businesses (and people in general) love getting things for free. Cut costs? Awesome. Save money? Super. So what if I were to tell you that there is a FREE way to make employees happier, more productive, and more likely to stay at your company?
Spoiler alert – it’s really not rocket science. Also, as a disclaimer, it may not work for everyone.
However, I discovered recently that there is something essential for my workplace happiness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>On Being a Woman in Tech</title>
      <link>https:/blog/202007on-being-a-woman-in-tech/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jul 2020 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https:/blog/202007on-being-a-woman-in-tech/</guid>
      <description>I am in a special, rare butterfly situation. At this moment, I only work with other women at Smarter Consulting. It’s me and four other smart, talented women who came from a variety of backgrounds, both in terms of our education and our careers. Some of us didn’t graduate college and some of us hold master’s degrees. Some of us have never worked in a strictly tech field (me).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Changing Careers During a Pandemic</title>
      <link>https:/blog/202006changing-careers-during-a-pandemic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 26 Jun 2020 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https:/blog/202006changing-careers-during-a-pandemic/</guid>
      <description>Growing up, I always knew I was going to become a teacher. Sure, my first choice was famous actress, but my solid backup plan was always elementary education. The only time I questioned my plan was when I entered freshman year of college and realized — not only did I not want to teach math and science, but that small children were kind of scary to me. So, after one semester, I changed my major to Secondary English Education and I was back on track for my life plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Greetings Earthlings</title>
      <link>https:/blog/202006greetings-earthlings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https:/blog/202006greetings-earthlings/</guid>
      <description>While secondary school-me could definitely imagine this, previous adult-me wouldn’t have guessed that I’d be taking up blogging again in my mid-30s. However, I’ve gone through a lot of transitions in my life lately, and since they’ve been good ones instead of traumatic ones, it occurred to me that other people might be interested in my journey as well.
Or maybe no one will be interested, but at least I will have a record of this time for myself because I am going through so much change.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
