<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>error handling on Lindsay T Shelton</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/tags/error-handling/</link><description>Recent content in error handling on Lindsay T Shelton</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 14:49:05 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blist.vercel.app/tags/error-handling/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Handling Locked M365 Files in Power Automate</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202306handling-locked-m365-files-in-power-automate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202306handling-locked-m365-files-in-power-automate/</guid><description>Sometimes, late at night, I awaken, covered in sweat, fresh from another nightmare about Power Automate flows that interact with SharePoint document libraries. Because what happens when you try to make changes to that document library, oh so innocently, when yet another innocent person has - gasp - the file open? Then Power Automate and SharePoint both respectively freak out at you and nothing can get done until that document is cleared out.</description></item><item><title>Frankenstein’s Monster Error Handling for Power Automate Cloud Flows</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202301frankensteins-monster-error-handling-for-power-automate-cloud-flows/</link><pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202301frankensteins-monster-error-handling-for-power-automate-cloud-flows/</guid><description>Be warned now – the content in this post is not 100% from my own brain and genius. In fact, it is cobbled together from three different geniuses who were kind enough to post their own methods for error handling in Power Automate over the years. I’ve judiciously bookmarked those posts, just waiting for when I had time and motivation to tackle error handling in my own flows, and today was that day.</description></item></channel></rss>