<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>sharepoint on Lindsay T Shelton</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/tags/sharepoint/</link><description>Recent content in sharepoint on Lindsay T Shelton</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 14:49:05 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blist.vercel.app/tags/sharepoint/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Handling Locked M365 Files in Power Automate</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202306handling-locked-m365-files-in-power-automate/</link><pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202306handling-locked-m365-files-in-power-automate/</guid><description>Sometimes, late at night, I awaken, covered in sweat, fresh from another nightmare about Power Automate flows that interact with SharePoint document libraries. Because what happens when you try to make changes to that document library, oh so innocently, when yet another innocent person has - gasp - the file open? Then Power Automate and SharePoint both respectively freak out at you and nothing can get done until that document is cleared out.</description></item><item><title>How To: Block Downloads with Stream on SharePoint</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202305how-to-block-downloads-with-stream-on-sharepoint/</link><pubDate>Wed, 24 May 2023 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202305how-to-block-downloads-with-stream-on-sharepoint/</guid><description>Anyone else stuck in a slow migration nightmare? That may be a tad dramatic, but…
I gotta be me, y’know?
Anyway, a big hurdle came up in our Stream Classic migration with a user who had a really good question. How can we block downloads with this new-fangled Stream option? It was a setting within Stream Classic that was being used by this department extenstively, and it was actually a legal requirement.</description></item><item><title>Utilizing the Contents of a SharePoint Image Column Elsewhere</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202302utilizing-the-contents-of-a-sharepoint-image-column-elsewhere/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Feb 2023 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202302utilizing-the-contents-of-a-sharepoint-image-column-elsewhere/</guid><description>So I recently met with someone who had a conundrum. They had a SharePoint list with an Image type column, relatively new-ish, and they wanted to post the contents of this column to Teams on a regular cadence, along with other text column content. They had tried every dynamic content option related to the Image column in Power Automate and nothing was working. I found quite a few blog posts that got us close, but not all the way.</description></item><item><title>Approvals Using SharePoint Groups</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202302approvals-using-sharepoint-groups/</link><pubDate>Wed, 15 Feb 2023 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202302approvals-using-sharepoint-groups/</guid><description>At my office, we have a lot of documents that undergo an annual review process. I was tasked pretty early on in my time here to help move this process from an Access database into the cloud. I could go on and on about the intricacies of what we set up, but I wanted to zero in on just one feature of the Power Automate flows that are set up: the group approval.</description></item></channel></rss>