<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>teams for education on Lindsay T Shelton</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/tags/teams-for-education/</link><description>Recent content in teams for education on Lindsay T Shelton</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 14:49:05 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blist.vercel.app/tags/teams-for-education/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How To: Share Your Screen AND See Your Audience in Microsoft Teams</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202009how-to-share-your-screen-and-see-your-audience-in-microsoft-teams/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Sep 2020 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202009how-to-share-your-screen-and-see-your-audience-in-microsoft-teams/</guid><description>If you are able to have more than one monitor, your life as virtual educator or work from home employee is a lot easier. One of those ways that life is easier is that you can both share your screen to present whatever information is relevant while also seeing your audience. It isn’t immediately clear, however, exactly how to see your audience at the same time, which is what this post will clear up for you.</description></item><item><title>How To: Change Team Names in Teams for Education</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202008how-to-change-team-names-in-teams-for-education/</link><pubDate>Thu, 06 Aug 2020 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202008how-to-change-team-names-in-teams-for-education/</guid><description>It’s almost fall and your IT department is swamped making hundreds if not thousands of Teams for teachers and their classes. However, sometimes their naming conventions they’ve utilized might not work best for teachers. We all know that IT doesn’t have the time to go in and fix the name of your Team to suit you best, so I’ve put together a tutorial for how you can make those changes yourself.</description></item></channel></rss>