<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>power bi on Lindsay T Shelton</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/tags/power-bi/</link><description>Recent content in power bi on Lindsay T Shelton</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:29:05 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blist.vercel.app/tags/power-bi/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Using Row-Level Security in Power BI and Power Automate - Part Two</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/20240105using_row_level_security_in_power_bi_and_power_automate_part_two/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jan 2024 09:29:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/20240105using_row_level_security_in_power_bi_and_power_automate_part_two/</guid><description>Make sure to check out Part One before reading this!
The Use Case A brief recap - I had 19 separate Power BI reports that, for various reasons, we decided to condense into one mega report using row-level security, or RLS. This gives each lab information about their storage - how much data are they storing, what does it cost, and a list of files that haven&amp;rsquo;t been updated in 3 years that might be prime targets for archiving.</description></item><item><title>Using Row-Level Security in Power BI and Power Automate</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/20240105using_row_level_security_in_power_bi_and_power_automate/</link><pubDate>Fri, 05 Jan 2024 11:29:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/20240105using_row_level_security_in_power_bi_and_power_automate/</guid><description>Power BI is not my normal wheelhouse, but when duty calls, I answer. I was recently asked to help update a report in Power BI that does all sorts of SQL calls to a database - how all of that works is a mystery to me. However, we were managing security by updating 19 different reports, one for each lab. This was a nightmare to maintain and update, as I discovered when my job was to go in and update all 19 of those reports.</description></item><item><title>Calling Multiple APIs in One Power BI Report (And All the Work-Arounds That Required)</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202302calling-multiple-apis-in-one-power-bi-report/</link><pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202302calling-multiple-apis-in-one-power-bi-report/</guid><description>So, this one was a lot more difficult than it should have been. It started with a plea for help on Twitter and a really helpful first blog post (created for me, so honored!) from Andy O’Donnell here. (He’s super nice, follow him on Twitter too!) Andy got me going, which I am SO grateful for… but then I ran into an error. And then another error. And another. You get the idea.</description></item><item><title>Track Your Productivity Using Outlook Categories and Power BI (Desktop)</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202206track-your-productivity-using-outlook-categories-and-power-bi/</link><pubDate>Sun, 12 Jun 2022 14:49:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202206track-your-productivity-using-outlook-categories-and-power-bi/</guid><description>Basic Category Visualization Start creating data to gather by creating your Outlook categories and categorizing all of your appointments and meetings over a period of time. Download Power BI Desktop for free and open it up Click “Get Data” Search for “Exchange” and connect to “Microsoft Exchange” Put in your email address that you want to connect The first time you do it, you will have a screen to connect via Exchange or Microsoft.</description></item></channel></rss>