<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>service-now on Lindsay T Shelton</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/tags/service-now/</link><description>Recent content in service-now on Lindsay T Shelton</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 08:29:05 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blist.vercel.app/tags/service-now/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>From Concept to Chatbot: ServiceNow with Copilot Studio - Part 4</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202409from_concept_to_chatbot_servicenow_with_copilot_studio_part4/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 08:29:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202409from_concept_to_chatbot_servicenow_with_copilot_studio_part4/</guid><description>Head back to the intro post to get the use case and architecture of the Copilot Studio bots I&amp;rsquo;ll be describing in these blog posts.
Next up is a shorter one for the shorter work week for some of us in the US - what if the user isn&amp;rsquo;t happy with any of the answers that our gen AI has provided for them and they want to open a ticket or incident with the help desk?</description></item><item><title>From Concept to Chatbot: ServiceNow with Copilot Studio - Part 3</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202409from_concept_to_chatbot_servicenow_with_copilot_studio_part3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 07 Oct 2024 08:29:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202409from_concept_to_chatbot_servicenow_with_copilot_studio_part3/</guid><description>Head back to the intro post to get the use case and architecture of the Copilot Studio bots I&amp;rsquo;ll be describing in these blog posts.
Next up is a big one - Conversational Boosting. Again, note that most of this content was adapted from this amazing video from Dewain Robinson here - this is just what I got working with the UI changes that have happened since the video first came out five months ago (now being October 2024, so who knows when the UI will change again).</description></item><item><title>From Concept to Chatbot: ServiceNow with Copilot Studio - Part 2</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202409from_concept_to_chatbot_servicenow_with_copilot_studio_part2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 10 Sep 2024 09:29:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202409from_concept_to_chatbot_servicenow_with_copilot_studio_part2/</guid><description>Head back to the intro post to get the use case and architecture of the Copilot Studio bots I&amp;rsquo;ll be describing in these blog posts, and head to part 1 to get a general overview of Copilot Studio, Topics, how I figured out troubleshooting the bot (the best you can at this point in Copilot Studio), and an overview of the Power Automate flows used in the initial POC I built.</description></item><item><title>From Concept to Chatbot: ServiceNow with Copilot Studio - Part 1</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202409from_concept_to_chatbot_servicenow_with_copilot_studio_part1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 09:29:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202409from_concept_to_chatbot_servicenow_with_copilot_studio_part1/</guid><description>Head back to the intro post to get the use case and architecture of the Copilot Studio bots I&amp;rsquo;ll be describing in these blog posts.
In this post, I&amp;rsquo;ll be giving a general overview of Copilot Studio, Topics which are the main thing I utilized (though there&amp;rsquo;s much more that can be used), how I figured out troubleshooting the bot, and the Power Automate flows used in the initial POC I built.</description></item><item><title>From Concept to Chatbot: ServiceNow with Copilot Studio Intro</title><link>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202409from_concept_to_chatbot_servicenow_with_copilot_studio_intro/</link><pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2024 08:29:05 -0500</pubDate><guid>https://blist.vercel.app/blog/202409from_concept_to_chatbot_servicenow_with_copilot_studio_intro/</guid><description>ServiceNow is a behemoth of a product, but it also has a robust API which means that we can suck it into our clutches&amp;hellip; I mean, ingest its data into our M365 ecosystem for a more seamless experience for our users. I knew all of this, but then I saw this amazing video from Dewain Robinson here, and when I say it got me started, I mean it gave me the use case, showed me the basics of interacting with Copilot Studio, and inspired me to keep building on that use case to make my own Copilot Studio ServiceNow bot.</description></item></channel></rss>